<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Théo Matussière</title>
    <link>https://theo-m.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Théo Matussière</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 09:45:14 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theo-m.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Joining Nabla</title>
      <link>https://theo-m.github.io/posts/nabla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 09:45:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theo-m.github.io/posts/nabla/</guid>
      <description>Met Alexandre Le Brun and Martin Raison during my internship at FAIR during summer &amp;lsquo;18. They left the office to start Nabla about a month after I&amp;rsquo;d arrived.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always had an interest in building things and looked for opportunities to be closer to the &amp;ldquo;real world&amp;rdquo;. So while I was writing my PhD proposal I started part-time there to be part of the adventure and try to help where I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emerging communications</title>
      <link>https://theo-m.github.io/posts/phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 09:46:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theo-m.github.io/posts/phd/</guid>
      <description>tldr: wrote a PhD proposition, did not do the PhD, the document is here
During the internship the PhD plan was growing more and more mature. So when it ended in the last days of August we moved on to write a formal thesis proposition.
That process was both exhilerating and stressful. Exhilerating because I basically made it into a shopping list of the topics I wanted to explore. Stressful because we were building a PhD between the Facebook AI labs and the Institut Jean-Nicod, a language philosophy lab at ENS, Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Internship at FAIR</title>
      <link>https://theo-m.github.io/posts/fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 09:46:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theo-m.github.io/posts/fair/</guid>
      <description>tldr: worked on dialogue evaluation, the report is here.
Joining FAIR was a long and winding road. During fall 2017 I had been reading some papers about emergent communication and found the question it raised resonated particularly with me. My masters degree required a research internship so I looked up who I could work with on such topic and found that Marco Baroni was at Facebook AI Research in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
